<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!-- ********************************************************************************************************************** -->
<!-- This file is automatically generated and should not be edited by hand. Editing this file directly is at your own risk. -->
<!-- ********************************************************************************************************************** -->
<JwstProposal schemaVersion="50" APTVersion="Version 2020.4  " PRDVersion="PRDOPSSOC-030" xmlns="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT" xmlns:mmrscge="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriMRSCrossGratingEngineering" xmlns:nsmsasd="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecMSAShortDetect" xmlns:nid="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissDark" xmlns:ncipri="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamIprImaging" xmlns:nif="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissFocus" xmlns:wfscfp="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/WfscFinePhasing" xmlns:nii="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissImaging" xmlns:mmimf="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriMimf" xmlns:mlrs="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriLRS" xmlns:mc="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriCoron" xmlns:md="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriDark" xmlns:nsfgwt="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecFilterGratingWheelTest" xmlns:wfscga="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/WfscGlobalAlignment" xmlns:nsil="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecInternalLamp" xmlns:idfu="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/IsimDictionaryFileUpdate" xmlns:mi="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriImaging" xmlns:nsimg="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecImaging" xmlns:niami="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissAmi" xmlns:niwfss="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissWfss" xmlns:ncif="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamInternalFlat" xmlns:nsfss="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecFixedSlitSpectroscopy" xmlns:fgsif="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/FgsInternalFlat" xmlns:ncef="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamExternalFlat" xmlns:ncei="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamEngineeringImaging" xmlns:niec="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissExternalCalibration" xmlns:nsmsam="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecMSAMasking" xmlns:niif="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissInternalFlat" xmlns:ncpili="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamPilImaging" xmlns:nsmsaa="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecMSAAnneal" xmlns:mcpc="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriCpc" xmlns:fgsec="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/FgsExternalCalibration" xmlns:nsd="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecDark" xmlns:nsf="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecFocus" xmlns:ns="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Instrument/Nirspec" xmlns:nisoss="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissSoss" xmlns:nsmimf="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecMimf" xmlns:ncts="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamTimeSeries" xmlns:ncd="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamDark" xmlns:mef="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriExternalFlat" xmlns:ncc="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamCoron" xmlns:ncf="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamFocus" xmlns:mmrs="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriMRS" xmlns:nci="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamImaging" xmlns:sk="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/StationKeeping" xmlns:wfscc="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/WfscCommissioning" xmlns:iat="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/IsimAsicTuning" xmlns:sr="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/SafeModeRecovery" xmlns:rtc="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/RealtimeCommanding" xmlns:nsfr="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecFocusReference" xmlns:ncw="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamWheelExercise" xmlns:nsbots="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecBrightObjectTimeSeries" xmlns:mann="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/MiriAnneal" xmlns:nsmos="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecMOS" xmlns:wfscco="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/WfscControlOnly" xmlns:ncgts="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamGrismTimeSeries" xmlns:wfsccp="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/WfscCoarsePhasing" xmlns:msa="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecMSA" xmlns:nsifus="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirspecIFUSpectroscopy" xmlns:ncwfss="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NircamWfss" xmlns:nifs="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/NirissFlatSuite" xmlns:fgsf="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/FgsFocus" xmlns:po="http://www.stsci.edu/JWST/APT/Template/PointingOnly">
    <ProposalInformation>
        <ProposalPhase>Approved</ProposalPhase>
        <Title>NIRISS CFM Focus Sweep</Title>
        <Abstract>The focus of NIRISS will be optimized with sweeps of the Coarse Focus Mechanism (CFM) on a field of well-separated, unblended stars. Confirmation images will be collected with the imaging filters, the GR150C/R and GR700XD grisms, and the NRM.</Abstract>
        <ProposalID>1085</ProposalID>
        <StsciEditNumber>11</StsciEditNumber>
        <ProposalCategorySubtype>NIRISS</ProposalCategorySubtype>
        <ProposalSize>SMALL</ProposalSize>
        <ProprietaryPeriod>C[6 Months]</ProprietaryPeriod>
        <Cycle>0</Cycle>
        <AllocatedTime>11.1</AllocatedTime>
        <ParallelNextCycle>false</ParallelNextCycle>
        <ParallelThirdCycle>false</ParallelThirdCycle>
        <NoSimilarSubmissions>false</NoSimilarSubmissions>
        <PdfAttachment>/Users/bethp/test.pdf</PdfAttachment>
        <ObservingDescription>ACTIVITY TITLE: NIRISS CFM Focus Sweep (NIS-010)

DESCRIPTION: The focus of NIRISS will be optimized with sweeps of the Coarse Focus Mechanism (CFM) on a field of well-separated, unblended stars. The field should be sufficiently dense and uniform to provide good spatial sampling over the entire FOV. Although the instrument will be launched at its best focus as determined from the ground test campaigns, some correction is required in orbit once the OTE is in its final configuration and NIRISS has reached its final operating temperature. 
    The flat Pick-Off Mirror (POM) is adjusted with a linear translation of the CFM of NIRISS – there is no correction for tip and tilt. As shown in Fig. 1, the FSW stop limits of the CFM defined in the PRD are -5.0 and +4.0 mm in the +V1 direction of the OTE frame, i.e., OTE mm, and it is commanded in relative (delta) steps with OSS scripts via an APT template. In the CFM frame, this range corresponds to -2.72 to +2.18 mm (conversion factor of 1.835). The CFM will scan a range of positions centered on the best ground-based focus in F158M + CLEAR, the baseline filter combination in all the ground cryo campaigns. At each CFM position, full-frame images will be collected without dithering followed by a 4-point dither pattern to reconstruct the PSFs in this filter. After analysis of the images, the CFM is commanded to the new position that produces the best focus over the field.
    The best focus will also be verified in the science modes with full-frame exposures in all the imaging filters, the GR150C/R and GR700XD grisms, and with the NRM. These will represent the “first light” observations in all the NIRISS modes with a focused instrument and will provide early, useful information on their performance (focus, spectral tilt and response, pupil shear, etc…) before proceeding to the “science” grism and NRM activities after the activities in the cold attitude. Although unlikely, a more refined second sweep may be performed about this new position and we allocate observations for these.
    The primary target is located in the CVZ-South and was selected based on several criteria, i.e., low dust extinction, appropriate density and range in J magnitudes and J-K colors, etc… (see Willott’s presentation on 12/13/2019).
    The FGS/NIRISS FSW remembers the last position of the CFM and that position is kept in RAM. But if the ICDH goes down for any reason, when the FGS/NIRISS FSW comes back up, it will only have the original, default launch value in memory. Hence, to preserve the new, best position of the CFM determined in this activity, a table load must be made via RTCP to the EEPROM to insure this new position becomes the default value. Alternatively, if this table load is not done, when the ICDH will come up, we will read the focus mechanism position. The first read will fail, as it will be compared with the stored default position. We then load the new position and read it again and all will be good. In fact, the OSS scripts are designed to operate this way after an ICDH start up – they allow one fail of the read at that time and load the read position and check again.

ACTIVITY EXECUTION METHOD: 
    1. OPE Commanding. Standard engineering proposal and commanding via the PPS and onboard scripts. 
    2. The table of the final CFM position,  INIS_ICE_CFM_CNFG_TBL.tbl, is loaded to RAM after placing NIRISS in STANDBY mode with inis_flt_mode_sel. The table is then loaded and dumped with ifsw_flt_table_load and ifsw_flt_table_dump and NIRISS is returned to IMAGING mode.  The associated SOPs are SOP_IFSW_517_TABLE_LOAD and SOP_IFSW_518_TABLE_DUMP. To permanently load the table to EEPROM, a limited lifetime item, the relevant RTCPs are icdh_flt_eeprom_lock_unlock and ifsw_flt_copytbl_eeprom described in the SOPs SOP_ICDH_LOCK_UNLOCK_EEPROM [TBC] and SOP_IFSW_500_COPY_TABLE_EEPROM.

PRE-REQUISITES AND DEPENDENCIES:
    1. The OTE commissioning activities have completed successfully and the primary is phased.
    2. The NIRISS engineering commissioning activities have executed successfully. This activity should then follow NIS-009 Gain and Linearity (1084).
    3. We request a hold of 72 hours after Observations 2 and 5 for data analysis (and possibly after the contingency Observations 7 and 10 if these are necessary).
 
CRITICAL START WINDOW? No
IF YES, NO-LATER-THAN START TIME: N/A

REAL-TIME CONTACT REQUIRED? Yes (for the table load to RAM and EEPROM)

DURATION: The total science duration of the primary observations (1 to 5) is therefore about 8.1 hours and the total charged time is 14.4 hours.

DATA REQUIREMENTS: The primary observations (1 to 5) will generate 26 GB. 

ANALYSIS &amp; EXPECTED RESULTS: TThe basic parameters of the stars will be measured at each setting of the CFM. These consist of: position, flux, peak counts, FWHM, encircled and ensquared energy, and entropy. A map of the best foci over the field will be produced and a fit to this plane will yield the optimal focus. The exposures collected in the grisms and the NRM, for the first time at the best focus of NIRISS but not necessarily in the standard configurations of their related science modes, will offer an early evaluation of their performance before executing the science activities later in the commissioning campaign. All the software related to this activity will have been written and tested on simulations of this field before launch. 
    The important telemetry mnemonics for the CFM are listed in Table 6 of the CAR. If these are at their expected values, then the CFM is operating nominally and no further action is required.
    After this activity, NIRISS will be at its best focus and ready for observations on astronomical targets in all its modes of operation.

IS YOUR INSTRUMENT DRIVING TELESCOPE POINTING? Yes 

IS THIS ACTIVITY PREFERABLY DONE IN PARALLEL? No

COMMENTS:
    1. A preview of the NIRISS focus field will be obtained in OTE-028 Pre-MIMF In Focus PSF Check (1165).
    2. If the position of the CFM was tweaked in NIS-032 MIMF SI Focus (1289), then the relative CFM steps may need to be revised with respect to the new position.
    3. The dither steps in pixels for a 4-point imaging pattern are: (0, 0), (6.0, 2.5), (2.5, 7.0), (-3.5, 4.5) and for the 4-point WFSS medium pattern: (0, 0), (8.0, 4.5), (3.5, 11.0), (-3.5, 7.5). 
    4. The position of the CFM is reported by the INIS_FMC_POS mnemonic in the engineering database and the FITS header keyword FOCUSPOS (OTE mm).
    5. The fine tolerance of the CFM is 16 resolver counts or 0.02 OTE mm.
    6. The stars “walk” by about 87 pixels and 6 pixels along the fast and slow axes, respectively, from one end of the sweep to the other.
    7. The breakdown of the observations is:

Observation 1: Primary Sweep
 
   The sweeps are commanded with the Focus template of APT. The steps are expressed relative to the starting position of the CFM. For this activity, then, this is simply the launch position adjusted for 0g, +0.338 OTE mm. The uncertainty on this value is about ±0.2 OTE mm. The range of motion of the mechanism is -5.0 to +4.0 OTE mm (Fig. 1 of the CAR). The preferred motion of direction of the CFM is towards decreasing OTE mm, i.e., from positive (+) to negative (–) OTE mm. A backlash correction is applied for each step along the non-preferred direction. Hence, it is always preferable to step in the preferred direction to minimize the mechanism usage and the duration of the sweep. 
    In APT, the relative steps of a full sweep are input in the template. An exposure is collected at the starting position and at each step of the sweep. At the end of the sweep, the CFM automatically returns to the starting position and another exposure is taken. Up to twenty positions can be commanded. All the exposures have the same number of integrations and groups. Dithers are not implemented. It may be worthwhile to overestimate the number of groups to ensure that enough counts are collected in the peak of the stars at the two ends of the sweeps, when the stars are the most defocused. The position of the CFM can be reset to a new position (and remain there) by specifying a single entry. In this case, an exposure is taken at the starting position and at the new position.
    The APT form includes a default sweep in relative steps. These are: [-0.4,-0.8,-1.2,-1.6,-2.0,2.0,1.6,1.2,0.8,0.4]. Twelve exposures at the following absolute (or physical) positions as returned by the INIS_FMC_POS mnemonic will be produced: [0.338 + 0.0,0.338 - 0.4,0.338 - 0.8,0.338 - 1.2,0.338 - 1.6,0.338 - 2.0,0.338 + 2.0,0.338 +1.6,0.338 + 1.2,0.338 + 0.8,0.338 + 0.4,0.338 + 0.0] = [0.34,-0.062,-0.46,-0.86,-1.26,-1.66,2.34,1.94,1.54,1.14,0.74,0.34] OTE mm (absolute). The total default range is therefore -1.66 to +2.34 OTE mm.
    But more “leverage” from larger deltas of the CFM is preferable for an accurate fitting of the focus curves, irrespective of the chosen metric. Hence, we adopt the symmetric sweep from CV3 (absolute): [+4.0,+3.0,+2.0,+1.0,+0.5,0.0,-0.5,-1.0,-2.0,-3.0,-4.0] OTE mm but centered on the launch position of +0.338 OTE mm: [+4.338,+3.338,+2.338,+1.338,+0.838,0.338,-0.162,-0.662,-1.662,-2.662,-3.662] OTE mm. But to ensure the limit of +4.0 OTE mm is not violated, we choose ± 3.9 OTE mm for the range limits. The smallest step is 0.5 OTE mm, slightly larger than the expected breadth of the focus over the whole field, 0.4 OTE mm (Zhou; private communication). The absolute steps are therefore:
[+3.9,+3.338,+2.338,+1.338,+0.838,0.338,-0.162,-0.662,-1.662,-2.662,-3.9] OTE mm. In relative offsets, these absolute positions correspond to:  [0.338-0.338=0.0,+3.9-0.338=+3.56,+3.338-0.338=+3.00,+2.338-0.338=2.00,+1.338-0.338=1.00,+0.838-0.338=0.50,0.338-0.338= 0.0,-0.162-0.338=-0.50,-0.662-0.338=-1.00,-1.662-0.338=-2.00,-2.662-0.338=-3.00,-3.9-0.338=-4.24,0.338-0.338=0.0], where we included the starting position at the beginning and end of the sweep. In APT, the sequence is therefore specified as: [-0.50,-1.00,-2.00,-3.00,-4.24,+3.56,+3.00,+2.00,+1.00,+0.50] (there is no need to specify the relative offset of 0.0 OTE mm). The initial and final exposures at 0.338 OTE mm will be automatically collected so in absolute or physical OTE mm, this sequence will generate exposures with these values of INIS_FMC_POS:
[+0.34,-0.16,-0.66,-1.66,-2.66,-3.9,+3.9,+3.34,+2.34,+1.34,+0.84,+0.34]. All the steps are in the preferred direction except for the movement between the two extremes. 

Observation 2: Dithered Imaging of the Field

    After the primary sweep, the CFM will have returned to its original launch position and the field is imaged with a 4-point dither pattern in the same filter to accurately reconstruct the PSFs. This is a simple observation with the External Calibration template in APT (Note: The Imaging template does not permit dithers).
    After this observation, we request a hold of 72 hours for data analysis and for measuring the new best focus.

Observation 3: Best Focus 

    Once the best focus has been determined from the primary sweep, we command the CFM to this new value by simply specifying a single relative step with the Focus template of APT. Exposures will be automatically taken at the starting position (old focus) and at the new position (new best focus). 
   After this observation, we request a hold of 8 hours to confirm the new best focus.

Observation 4: Confirmation in Imaging, NRM, GR700XD

    For confirmation of this new best focus, we image the field in all the filters as well as in the wheel elements of the SOSS and AMI modes, GR700XD + CLEAR and NRM + F480M. This observation is implemented with the External Calibration template. The 0th-order of the GR700XD spectral traces will be detected for the first, and perhaps only, time in the entire JWST mission. By directly comparing the count rate of the stars in the NRM + F480M exposure with those in a contemporaneous CLEARP + F480M exposure, the flux attenuation of the NRM will be directly measured and compared with the ground measurements.

Observation 5: Confirmation in GR150C/R

     For confirmation of the best focus in the GR150C/R, we observe the field in the four broad-band blocking filters F090W, F115W, F150W, and F200W. We implement this observation with the WFSS template with a dither pattern that will be popular in the GO and GTO programs, i.e., MEDIUM 8-point. This dither pattern is ideal to correct the images of bad pixels, CR hits, etc…. Exercising this science template early in commissioning is also important to validate the end-to-end processing of the WFSS data. The tilt and shape of the traces over the FOV will also be measured and the field-dependent curvatures defined as polynomials in JSON files for the 1D extraction step of the pipeline will be updated. The exposures will also be examined for any evidence of delamination and ghosts. It is important that this observation be made before pointing to the cold attitude since this two-week period will allow the NIRISS team to analyze the data in detail before proceeding to the following science activities.
    If the tilts of the grism spectra need to be adjusted, the contingency activities NIS-030-C GR700XD Tilt Adjustment (1103) and NIS-031-C GR150C/R Tilt Adjustment (1104) may need to be executed to redefine the center position of GR150C, GR150R, and GR700XD in their wheels.
    After this observation, we request a hold of 72 hours to examine the data and confirm that the new best focus is satisfactory in all the NIRISS science modes.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Observation 6: Secondary Sweep (Contingency)

    If a satisfactory focus could not be achieved or if fine-tuning is necessary, we perform a short, secondary sweep about the new focus position set in Observation 3. In APT, we choose relative steps of: [-0.20,-0.50,-1.00,-2.00,+2.00,+1.00,+0.50,+0.20]. The starting and final positions of the CFM are the new focus position set in Observation 3. Additional exposures will be collected at the beginning and end of the sweep.

Observation 7: Dithered Imaging of the Field (Contingency)

   This is a repeat of Observation 2. After the secondary sweep, the field is imaged with a 4-point dither pattern to accurately reconstruct the PSFs at the new focus. This is a simple observation with the External Calibration template in APT.
    After this observation, we request a hold of 72 hours for data analysis and for measuring the new best focus.

Observation 8: Best Focus (Contingency)

    This is a repeat of Observation 3. Once the best focus has been refined from the secondary sweep, we command the CFM to this new value by simply specifying a single relative step with the Focus template of APT. Exposures will be automatically taken at the starting position (old focus) and at the new position (new best focus).
  After this observation, we request a hold of 8 hours to confirm the new best focus.
 
Observation 9: Confirmation in Imaging, NRM, GR700XD (Contingency)

    For confirmation of this refined best focus in imaging, NRM, and GR700XD, we repeat Observation 4. 

Observation 10: Confirmation in GR150C/R (Contingency)

    For confirmation of the best focus in the GR150C/R grisms, we repeat Observation 5.  

    After this observation is complete, we request a hold of 72 hours to examine the data carefully and confirm that the refined best focus is satisfactory.

Feb 15, 2020.</ObservingDescription>
        <PrincipalInvestigator>
            <InvestigatorAddress>
                <UniqueID>4693</UniqueID>
                <Country>USA</Country>
                <EMail>martel@stsci.edu</EMail>
                <Institution>Space Telescope Science Institute</Institution>
                <USState>MD</USState>
                <ESAMember>false</ESAMember>
                <CSAMember>false</CSAMember>
                <FirstName>Andre</FirstName>
                <Honorific>Dr.</Honorific>
                <LastName>Martel</LastName>
                <Retired>false</Retired>
            </InvestigatorAddress>
            <Contact>true</Contact>
            <GTOTimeSource></GTOTimeSource>
        </PrincipalInvestigator>
        <CoInvestigator>
            <CoPI>false</CoPI>
            <InvestigatorAddress>
                <UniqueID>3822</UniqueID>
                <Country>USA</Country>
                <EMail>goudfroo@stsci.edu</EMail>
                <Institution>Space Telescope Science Institute</Institution>
                <USState>MD</USState>
                <ESAMember>false</ESAMember>
                <CSAMember>false</CSAMember>
                <FirstName>Paul</FirstName>
                <Honorific>Dr.</Honorific>
                <LastName>Goudfrooij</LastName>
                <Retired>false</Retired>
            </InvestigatorAddress>
            <AdminUSPI>false</AdminUSPI>
            <Contact>false</Contact>
        </CoInvestigator>
        <CoInvestigator>
            <CoPI>false</CoPI>
            <InvestigatorAddress>
                <UniqueID>24082</UniqueID>
                <Country>USA</Country>
                <EMail>maria.b.vilacostas@nasa.gov</EMail>
                <Institution>GSFC/SGT</Institution>
                <USState>MD</USState>
                <ESAMember>false</ESAMember>
                <CSAMember>false</CSAMember>
                <FirstName>Begona</FirstName>
                <Honorific>Dr.</Honorific>
                <LastName>Vila</LastName>
                <Retired>false</Retired>
            </InvestigatorAddress>
            <AdminUSPI>false</AdminUSPI>
            <Contact>false</Contact>
        </CoInvestigator>
        <CoInvestigator>
            <CoPI>false</CoPI>
            <InvestigatorAddress>
                <UniqueID>26988</UniqueID>
                <Country>CAN</Country>
                <EMail>julia.zhou2@honeywell.com</EMail>
                <Institution>Honeywell Aerospace</Institution>
                <USState>ON</USState>
                <ESAMember>false</ESAMember>
                <CSAMember>true</CSAMember>
                <FirstName>Julia</FirstName>
                <LastName>Zhou</LastName>
                <Retired>false</Retired>
            </InvestigatorAddress>
            <AdminUSPI>false</AdminUSPI>
            <Contact>false</Contact>
        </CoInvestigator>
    </ProposalInformation>
    <VisitStatuses>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085001001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="12"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085002001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="4"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085003001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="2"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085004001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="56"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085005001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="80"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085006001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="10"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085007001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="4"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085008001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="2"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085009001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="56"/>
        <VisitStatus VisitId="01085010001" Status="IMPLEMENTATION" NumPointings="80"/>
    </VisitStatuses>
    <Targets>
        <Target xsi:type="FixedTargetType" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
            <Number>1</Number>
            <TargetName>NIRISS-FOCUS-FIELD</TargetName>
            <TargetArchiveName>NIRISS Focus Field</TargetArchiveName>
            <TargetID>NIRISS-FOCUS-FIELD</TargetID>
            <RAProperMotion></RAProperMotion>
            <DecProperMotion></DecProperMotion>
            <RAProperMotionUnits></RAProperMotionUnits>
            <DecProperMotionUnits></DecProperMotionUnits>
            <Extended>Unknown</Extended>
            <Category>Calibration</Category>
            <Keywords>Focus test</Keywords>
            <EquatorialCoordinates Value="05 31 11.8800 -68 46 42.00">
                <RAUncertainty>
                    <Value></Value>
                    <Units>Arcsec</Units>
                </RAUncertainty>
                <DecUncertainty>
                    <Value></Value>
                    <Units>Arcsec</Units>
                </DecUncertainty>
            </EquatorialCoordinates>
            <BackgroundTargetReq>false</BackgroundTargetReq>
            <TargetConfirmationRun>true</TargetConfirmationRun>
        </Target>
    </Targets>
    <PureParallelSlots/>
    <DataRequests>
        <ObservationGroup>
            <Label>Primary</Label>
            <Observation AutoTarget="false">
                <Number>1</Number>
                <TargetID>1 NIRISS-FOCUS-FIELD</TargetID>
                <Instrument>NIRISS</Instrument>
                <Template>
                    <niwfss:NirissWfss>
                        <niwfss:PrimaryDithers>4</niwfss:PrimaryDithers>
                        <niwfss:DitherSize>MEDIUM</niwfss:DitherSize>
                        <niwfss:ExposureList>
                            <niwfss:ExposureSequences>
                                <niwfss:Sequence>GR150C</niwfss:Sequence>
                                <niwfss:Filter>F150W</niwfss:Filter>
                                <niwfss:DiExposure>
                                    <niwfss:ReadoutPattern>NIS</niwfss:ReadoutPattern>
                                    <niwfss:Groups>4</niwfss:Groups>
                                    <niwfss:Integrations>1</niwfss:Integrations>
                                    <niwfss:EtcId></niwfss:EtcId>
                                    <niwfss:ShouldDither>true</niwfss:ShouldDither>
                                </niwfss:DiExposure>
                                <niwfss:GrismExposure>
                                    <niwfss:ReadoutPattern>NIS</niwfss:ReadoutPattern>
                                    <niwfss:Groups>4</niwfss:Groups>
                                    <niwfss:Integrations>1</niwfss:Integrations>
                                    <niwfss:EtcId></niwfss:EtcId>
                                </niwfss:GrismExposure>
                            </niwfss:ExposureSequences>
                            <niwfss:ExposureSequences>
                                <niwfss:Sequence>GR150R</niwfss:Sequence>
                                <niwfss:Filter>F150W</niwfss:Filter>
                                <niwfss:DiExposure>
                                    <niwfss:ReadoutPattern>NIS</niwfss:ReadoutPattern>
                                    <niwfss:Groups>4</niwfss:Groups>
                                    <niwfss:Integrations>1</niwfss:Integrations>
                                    <niwfss:EtcId></niwfss:EtcId>
                                    <niwfss:ShouldDither>true</niwfss:ShouldDither>
                                </niwfss:DiExposure>
                                <niwfss:GrismExposure>
                                    <niwfss:ReadoutPattern>NIS</niwfss:ReadoutPattern>
                                    <niwfss:Groups>4</niwfss:Groups>
                                    <niwfss:Integrations>1</niwfss:Integrations>
                                    <niwfss:EtcId></niwfss:EtcId>
                                </niwfss:GrismExposure>
                            </niwfss:ExposureSequences>
                        </niwfss:ExposureList>
                    </niwfss:NirissWfss>
                </Template>
                <ScienceDuration>2752</ScienceDuration>
                <CoordinatedParallel>false</CoordinatedParallel>
                <SpecialRequirements/>
                <MosaicParameters>
                    <Rows>1</Rows>
                    <Columns>1</Columns>
                    <RowOverlapPercent>10.0</RowOverlapPercent>
                    <ColumnOverlapPercent>10.0</ColumnOverlapPercent>
                    <SkewDegreesX>0.0</SkewDegreesX>
                    <SkewDegreesY>0.0</SkewDegreesY>
                    <MosaicTiles TileNumber="1">
                        <TileState>Tile Included</TileState>
                    </MosaicTiles>
                    <MosaicTileOrder>DEFAULT</MosaicTileOrder>
                </MosaicParameters>
                <ObservingWindowsContainer>
                    <MOSSStartDate></MOSSStartDate>
                    <MOSSEndDate></MOSSEndDate>
                    <MOSSShowWindows>false</MOSSShowWindows>
                </ObservingWindowsContainer>
                <Visit Number="1"/>
            </Observation>
        </ObservationGroup>
    </DataRequests>
    <LinkingRequirements/>
</JwstProposal>
